{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of The Walking Dead.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Rick?",
      "answers": ["Leader", "Doctor", "Soldier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Terminus?",
      "answers": ["Sanct", "Prison", "Farm"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Michonne?",
      "answers": ["Samurai", "Doctor", "Nurse"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Lucille?",
      "answers": ["Bat", "Knife", "Gun"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Negan?",
      "answers": ["Villain", "Hero", "Leader"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Alexandria?",
      "answers": ["Safe", "Danger", "Battle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Daryl?",
      "answers": ["Hunter", "Doctor", "Pilot"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is The Governor?",
      "answers": ["Leader", "Doctor", "Hunter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Carl?",
      "answers": ["Son", "Brother", "Friend"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Carol?",
      "answers": ["Mother", "Sister", "Daughter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Hilltop?",
      "answers": ["Community", "Town", "City"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Glenn?",
      "answers": ["Scout", "Doctor", "Hunter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Maggie?",
      "answers": ["Leader", "Scout", "Doctor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a Walker?",
      "answers": ["Zombie", "Human", "Animal"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Ezekiel?",
      "answers": ["King", "Doctor", "Soldier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Woodbury?",
      "answers": ["Town", "City", "Farm"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Eugene?",
      "answers": ["Scient", "Hunter", "Leader"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rosita?",
      "answers": ["Soldier", "Doctor", "Nurse"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Savior?",
      "answers": ["Group", "Weapon", "Leader"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Alpha?",
      "answers": ["Leader", "Doctor", "Hunter"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
